CONTACT

Telephone | 5857045630 Email | brennnann@gmail.com



Full Stack Software Engineer

I am a full stack software engineer specializing in frontend development. I graduated the University of Texas full stack software development program in 2020. Originally from Rochester New York, I moved to Austin shortly after I graduated a music performance program. Over time I began to notice the similarities between coding and musical notation. They both required a great deal of discipline, attention to detail, and the ability to create anything you could imagine.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React.js, Redux, JQuery, MySQL, PHP, Node.js, Heroku, Git, CRUD operations, RESTful API's Mongo Db, PWA, and Security.

......

EDUCATION

2020 | University of Texas | Austin, TX

Full Stack Software Development Bootcamp

2012 | Finger Lakes Community College | Canandaigua, NY

Associates of Science (Music Performance)

EXPERIENCE

Winter Haven Capital LLC | Austin, TX | 2019- Present | Front-End Software Developer

- Develop a dynamic investment trading application.
- Insure the software is compatible and responsive for all devices .
- Deploy various frameworks to enhance the users experience.

Out of this World Music School | Austin, TX | 2016 - 2018 | Percussion / Piano Instructor

- Taught piano / percussion / composition/ theory.
- · Instructed all ages.
- · Worked alongside students to achieve their goals.

Alamo Draft House South Lamar | South Lamar, TX | 2012 - 2016 | Shift leader, Trainer, Server

• Delegated tasks to servers to complete during shifts.

REFERENCES

Available upon request.